Finding Aid for the CBS Inc. Film and Television Collection PASC-M.0072
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Programs, Series 4.
  - CBS School Break -- Sound Recordings, 1986 March-June; Subseries 23.; 9 sound recordings
    - God, the Universe and Hot Fudge Sundaes (Logs 5950-5946), 1986 March 6; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1087, Folder 5)
      On container, "CED/3-6-86/R320/Logs 5950-5946 DD/School Break "God the Universe and Hot Fudge Sundays"."
    - God, The Universe and Hot Fudge Sundaes, 1986 March 6; Cassette tape (Box 1852)
    - My Dissident Mom, 1986 June 19 (Box 1852)
      All master takes.
      Cassette tape. 4 copies, all with labels reading " 6/9/86; CBS; all master takes."
  - CBS Sports -- Sound Recordings, 1975 September 6-10; Subseries 24.; 2 sound recordings
    - NFL Today Theme Title, 1975 September 6; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 997, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS Sports/"NFL Today" Theme Title."
    - NFL Today Theme Title (logs 1034, 1041, 1042), 1975 September 10; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1153, Folder 10)
      On container, "CTN/9-10-75/R41C/CTN 600 LOGS 1042, 1034, 1041 DD 4-6/CBS Sports NFL Today Theme Title."
  - CBS Sports Spectacular -- Sound Recordings, 1975 October 10; Subseries 25.; 1 sound recordings
    - Logs 1054-1093, 1975 October 10; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 997, Folder 1)
      On container, "CTN/10-10-75/16 Trk/Logs 1054-1093/CBS Sports Spectacular."
  - CBS Story Break -- Papers, Subseries 26.
    - What Happened in Hamelin -- Papers, 1986 March 7 - 1987 October 21; 8 pages (Box 1860, Folder 28)
      Includes: memos; music clearance sheets, and film dubbing reports.
    - Yen Shen -- Papers, 1985 March 21 - June 12; 53 pages (Box 1860, Folder 30)
      Includes: music notes; music cue sheets; invoices; music clearance sheets; permission for use agreements, and film dubbing reports.
      Production no. 0143-8402.
  - CBS Story Break -- Recording Logs, Subseries 27.
    - What Happened in Hamelin (logs 5952-6014), 1986 April 1; 24 pages (Box 1860, Folder 29)
      Includes cues, timings, and timing sheets.
      Production no. 0201-4418.
    - Yen Shen (logs 4835-4902)-- Recording Logs, 1985 March 14; 27 pages (Box 1860, Folder 31)
      Includes: cues, timings, notes on orchestration, etc.
  - CBS Story Break -- Scores, Subseries 28.
    Items are arranged alphabetically by episode title.
    - What Happened in Hamlin, 270 p. (Box 1849)
    - Mama Don't Allow, 85 p. (Box 1850)
      Production no. 1208-0206
    - Yen Shen, 138 p. (Box 1850)
  - CBS Story Break -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 29.
    - Mama Don't Allow, 1987 April 28; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 961, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS ENT/Bob Drasnin/Mama Dont Allow/4-28-87/MOO+POD/24 Trk/Dolby/250/+3 15IPS/Reel 3."
    - Mama Don't Allow, 1985 October 18; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 961, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS ENT/Bob Drasnin/Mama Dont Allow/10-18-85/MOO+POD/24 Trk/Dolby/250/+3 15IPS/Reel 2."
    - Mama Don't Allow, 1985 October 18; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 1015, Folder 1)
      On container, "CBS Ent/Bob Drasnin/"Mama Dont Allow"/10-18-85/MOD + POD/24/Dolby/250/+3 15 IPS/Reel 1."
    - Mama Don't Allow, 86 p. (Box 1849)
    - Mama Don't Allow, 1985 October 20; open reel audio tape (Box 1082, Folder 12)
      On container, "CED/10-20-85/R194/DDRemix/Storybreak "Mama Don't Allow"."
    - Mama Don't Allow -- Music Cues, 1987 April 28; open reel audio tape (Box 1069, Folder 8)
      On container, ""Mama Don't Allow"/Music Cues/R336/4-28-87."
    - Mama Don't Allow (Logs 5450-5481), 1985 October 18; open reel audio tape (Box 1082, Folder 13)
      On container, "CED/10-18-85/R192/Logs 5450-5481/Storybreak "Mama Don't Allow" PreScore."
    - Mama Don't Allow -- Music Cues, 1987 April 28; open reel audio tape (Box 1069, Folder 9)
      On container, ""Mama Don't Allow"/Music Cues/R335/4-28-87."
    - What Happened in Hamlin (Logs 6013-6016), 1986 April 1; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1077, Folder 1)
      On container, "CED/4-1-86/R323/Logs 6013-6016/Storybreak "What Happened In Hamlin"."
    - What Happened in Hamlin (Logs 5984-6012), 1986 April 1; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1077, Folder 4)
      On container, "CED/4-1-86/R322/Logs 5984-6012/Storybreak "What Happened In Hamlin"."
    - Harry the Fat Bear Spy (Logs 5404-5449), 1985 September 26; open reel audio tape (Box 1082, Folder 14)
      On container, "CED/9-26-85/R244/Logs 5404-5449/Storybreak "Harry The Fat Bear Spy"."
    - Harry the Fat Bear Spy (Logs 5351-5403), 1985 September 26; open reel audio tape (Box 1082, Folder 15)
      On container, "CED/9-26-85/R243/Logs 5351-5403/Storybreak "Harry The Fat Bear Spy"."
    - Yeh Shen (Logs 4839-4902), 1985 March 14; open reel audio tape (Box 1083, Folder 1)
      On container, "CED/3-14-85/R219/logs 4839-4902/DD/Print Takes Only/StoryBreak/"Yeh Shen"." Production no. 0143-8402.
    - Yeh Shen (Logs 4835-4864), 1985 March 14; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1084, Folder 6)
      On container, "CED/3-14-85/R171/logs 4835-4864/Storybreak-"Yeh Shen"." Production no. 0143-8402.
    - Yeh Shen (Logs 4865-4891), 1985 March 14; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1084, Folder 7)
      On container, "CED/3-14-85/R172/logs 4865-4891/Storybreak/"Yeh-Shen"." Production no. 0143-8402.
    - Yeh Shen (Logs 4892-4902), 1985 March 14; open reel audio tape ,1/2 in. (Box 1084, Folder 8)
      On container, "CED/3-14-85/R173X/logs 4892-4902/Storybreak/"Yeh-Shen"." Production no. 0143-8402.
    - What Happened in Hamelin (Logs 5952-5983), 1986 April 1; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1087, Folder 8)
      On container, "CED/4-1-86/R321/Logs 5952-5983/Storybreak "What Happened in Hamelin"."
    - Harry, the Fat Bear Spy (Logs 5404-5449), 1985 September 26; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1091, Folder 16)
      On container, "CED/9-26-85/R191/Logs 5404-5449/Storybreak "Harry, The Fat Bear Spy"."
    - Harry, the Fat Bear Spy (Logs 5351-5403), 1985 September 26; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1091, Folder 17)
      On container, "CED/9-26-85/R190/Logs 5351-5403/Storybreak "Harry, The Fat Bear Spy"."
    - Zucchini (Logs 5078-5089), 1985 April 15; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1128, Folder 1)
      On container, "CED/4-15-85/R179/LOGS 5078-5089/Storybreak "Zucchini"."
    - Zucchini (Logs 5027-5052), 1985 April 15; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1128, Folder 2)
      On container, "CED/4-15-85/R177/LOGS 5027-5052/Storybreak "Zucchini"."
    - Zucchini (Logs 5053-5077), 1985 April 15; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1128, Folder 3)
      On container, "CED/4-15-85/R178/LOGS 5053-5077/Storybreak "Zucchini"."
    - Zucchini (Logs 5027-5052), 1985 April 15; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1128, Folder 16)
      On container, "CED/4-15-85/R226/LOGS 5027-5052/Storybreak "Zucchini"."
    - Zucchini (Logs 5078-5089), 1985 April 15; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1130, Folder 19)
      On container, "CED/4-15-85/R228/LOGS 5078-5089/Storybreak "Zucchini"."
    - Zucchini (Logs 5053-5077), 1985 April 15; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1130, Folder 20)
      On container, "CED/4-15-85/R227/LOGS 5053-5077/Storybreak "Zucchini"."
  - Checkmate -- Scores, Subseries 175.
    - Theme (Box 118)
  - Cimarron Strip -- Sound Recordings, 1967; Subseries 30.
    Western
    - Logs 518-533, July 11, 1967; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1144, Folder 12)
      On container, "CBS/Cimarron 0202/R26A/LOG 518 To 533/7-11-67."
  - City -- Scripts, Subseries 31.
    - Yeh Shen (Logs 4839-4902), 3/14/1985; open reel audio tape (Box 1083, Folder 1)
      On container, "CED/3-14-85/R219/logs 4839-4902/DDD Print Takes Only/Storybreak/"Yeh Shen"."
    - Just a Passing Dad, April 19, 1990; 51 p. (Box 1762)
      Teleplay by Jennifer Heath, Amy Sherman and Paul Haggis. Story by Jennifer Heath and Amy Sherman.
      Episode 13. Table draft. Production #9013. Includes a tentative shooting schedule.
    - With a Song in Your Heart and a Knife in Your Back, April 19, 1990; 45 p. (Box 1762)
      Written by Paul Haggis.
      Episode 12. Table draft. Production #9015. Includes a tentative shooting schedule. Four copies.
  - Climax -- Recording Logs, Subseries 32.
    Also known as "Climax Mystery Theater."
    - Season 4, Episode 20: The Thief With the Big Blue Eyes, 1958 March 31 (Box 1157, Folder 1)
      On item, "The Thief With The Big Blue Eyes / Prod. #57-23 / Music Log sent: 31 Mar. '58."
    - Season 4, Episode 25: Shooting for the Moon, 1958 May 7 (Box 1157, Folder 2)
      On item, "Shooting for the Moon / Prod. #57-30 / Music Log sent: 7 May '58."
    - Season 4, Episode 23: On the Take, 1958 April 10 (Box 1157, Folder 3)
      On item, "On The Take / Prod. #57-27 / Music Log sent: 10 Apr. '58."
    - Season 4, Episode 28: The Disappearance of Daphne, 1958 May 20 (Box 1157, Folder 4)
      On item, "Disappearance Of Daphne / Prod. #57-33 / Music Log sent: 20 May '58."
    - Season 4, Episode 19: Albert Anastasia - His Life and Death, 1958 March 31 (Box 1158, Folder 6)
      On item, "Albert Anastasia / Prod. #57-22 / Music Log sent: 31 Mar. '58."
    - Season 4, Episode 27: The Big Success, 1958 May 16 (Box 1159, Folder 6)
      On item, "The Big Success / Prod. #57-32 / Music Log Sent: 16 May '58."
    - Season 4, Episode 34: Cabin B-13, 1958 July 10 (Box 1171, Folder 3)
      On item, "Cabin B-13 / Prod. #57-39 / Music Log sent: 10 July '58."
    - Season 4, Episode 26: The Deadly Tattoo, 1958 May 7 (Box 1172, Folder 2)
      On item, "Deadly Tattoo / Prod. #57-31 / Music Log sent: 7 May '58."
    - Season 4, Episode [24 or 32]: The Volcano Seat, 1958 July 10 (Box 1172, Folder 3)
      On item, "The Volcano Seat / Prod. #57-37 / Music Log sent: 10 July '58." "The Volcano Seat" number 1 was episode 24; number 2 was episode 32.
    - Season 4, Episode 33: The House of Doubt, 1958 July 10 (Box 1172, Folder 4)
      On item, "House of Doubt / Prod. #57-38 / Music Log sent: 10 July '58."
    - Season 4, Episode 30: The Push Button Giant, 1958 June 17 (Box 1172, Folder 5)
      On item, "Push Button Giant / Prod. #57-35 / Music Log sent: 17 June '58."
    - Season 4, Episode 31: Spider Web, 1958 June 13 (Box 1172, Folder 6)
      On item, "Spider Web / Prod. #57-36 / Music Log sent: 13 June '58."
  - Coming of Age - Sound Recordings, 1988; Subseries 185.
    Plot: Dick and Ginny Hale move from Pittsburgh to an Arizona retirement community to spend their golden years in peace and tranquility.
    - Coming of Age, 1971 November 23; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. tape (Box 1117, Folder 11)
      On container, "Coming Of Age/Roll #1/Tk 1-36/23 Nov 71."
    - Coming of Age, 1971 November 23; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1117, Folder 12)
      On container, "Coming Of Age/Roll #2/Tk 39-47/23 Nov 71."
  - The Defenders -- Scores, Subseries 170.
    - Theme (Box 118)
      Score no: CPN5982.
  - Designing Women -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 33.
    - Unidentified, 1986 May 7; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1154, Folder 7)
      On container, "Mike Hammer/Designing Women/Mike Hammer Main Title/Mike Hammer End Credits/M.T. Long Version "Designing Women"/M.T. Short Ver. "Designing Women"/E.C. Designing Women."
  - Dealer's Choice -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 34.
    Game show.
    - Mix Reel, November 4, 1985; 2 in. tape (Box 1032, Folder 2)
      On container, "Dealer's Choice/Mix Reel."
  - Dinah -- Sound Recordings, 1974 August 21; Subseries 35.; 1 sound recordings
    - Logs 1-29, 1974 August 21; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1149, Folder 6)
      On container, "CTS/8-21-74/R1 DD/LOGS 1-29/"Dinah" (Demo)."
  - Dirty Sally -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 36.
    - Main Title, January 9, 1973; open reel audio tape (Box 945, Folder 21)
      On container, "CBS Dirty Sally Main Title Dubb Version."
    - Unidentified, December 28, 1973; open reel audio tape (Box 1053, Folder 10)
      Description on box is scratched out. On container, "Dirty Sally Copy/12-28-73/15 IPS."
    - Log 836, November 12, 1973; open reel audio tape (Box 945, Folder 17)
      On container, "CBS/11-12-73/R60A/Logs 836/Dirty Sally M.T. (Morford Version)."
    - Logs 836 & 840, November 12,1973; open reel audio tape (Box 943, Folder 7)
      On container, "CBS/11-12-73/R43A/Logs 836 & 840/Dirty Sally - M.T. Demo."
    - Logs 1013-1022, December 20, 1973; open reel audio tape (Box 950, Folder 20)
      On container, "CBS/12-20-73/R55A/Logs 1013-1022/SA - "Format Material"."
    - Log 1022, December 20, 1973; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1120, Folder 12)
      On container, "CBS/12-20-73/R59A/LOG 1022/Dirty Sally M.T. (Rodriguez Version)."
    - Logs 1032-1097, December 20, 1973; open reel audio tape (Box 945, Folder 18)
      On container, "CBS/12-20-73/R56A/Logs 1032-1097/SA - "Right of Way" SA - "Honk 'Em"."
    - Logs 1098-1145, December 20, 1973; open reel audio tape (Box 945, Folder 19)
      On container, "CBS/12-20-73/R57A/Logs 1098-1145/SA - "Honk 'Em", SA - "Hanging of Cyrus"."
    - Logs 1146-1165, December 20, 1973; open reel audio tape (Box 945, Folder 20)
      On container, "CBS/12-20-73/R58A/Logs 1146-1165/SA - "Hanging of Cyrus"."
    - Logs 1166-1204, January 1, 1974; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1120, Folder 8)
      On container, "CBS/1-4-74/R61A/LOGS 1166-1204/SA "End Credits" "Worthless"."
    - Logs 1205-1252, January 1, 1974; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1120, Folder 9)
      On container, "CBS/1-4-74/R62A/Logs 1205-1252/SA "Worthless" "Much Ado"."
    - Logs 1253-1255, January 4, 1974; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1120, Folder 11)
      On container, "CBS/1-4-74/R63A/LOGS 1253-1255/SA "Much Ado"."
    - Logs 1317-1327, January 9, 1974; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1120, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS/1-9-74/R67A/LOGS 1317-1327/SA "Old Soldier" (Bugle Cues)."
    - Logs 1358-1386, January 15, 1974; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1120, Folder 7)
      On container, "CBS/1-15-74/R70A/LOGS 1358-1386/SA "Convict"."
    - Logs 1442-1456, January 21, 1974; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1120, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/1-21-74/R73A/LOGS 1442-1456/SA "Horse Dif Color"."
    - Logs 1457-1492, January 21, 1974; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1134, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS/1-21-74/R74A/LOGS 1457-1492/SA "Too Long Wait"."
    - Logs 1493-1501, January 21, 1974; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1134, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS/1-21-74/R75A/LOGS 1493-1501/SA "Too Long Wait"."
    - Logs 1589-1599, January 28, 1974; open reel audio tape (Box 955, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS/1-28-74/R80A/Logs 1589-1599/GS - "Iron Blood Courage", SA - "Glitters" 2 PNO Cues."
    - Logs 1689-1765, March 5, 1974; open reel audio tape (Box 955, Folder 10)
      On container, "CBS/3-5-74/R85A/Logs 1698-1765/GS - "Yeller Horse", SA - "Wimmen's Rights"."
    - Logs 1818-1819, March 18, 1974; open reel audio tape (Box 955, Folder 17)
      On container, "CTN/3-18-74/R92A/Logs 1818-1819/SA - "Never Saw Pacific" (Wedding March - Organ)."
  - Doc -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 37.
    - Log 1095, 1975 November 24; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 1009, Folder 1)
      On container, "CTN/11-24-75/CTN 605/Log 1095/"Doc" Promo."
    - Log 1095, November 24,1975; open reel audio tape (Box 1108, Folder 10)
      On container, "CTN/11-24-75/R44DD/LOG 1095/"Doc" Promo."
    - Logs 1043-1053, September 8, 1975; open reel audio tape (Box 1108, Folder 11)
      On container, "CTN/9-8-75/R42A/LOGS 1043-1053/Promos: "Doc" "Kojak/Bronk"."
  - Dog Face -- Scores, Subseries 162.
    - Pilot Episode, manuscript score; ozalid (Box 99)
      Score no: CPN5813
  - Doris Day Show -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 38.
    - Logs 365-388, 1969 July 18; open reel audio tape (Box 939, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/0311-1615 0356/R14A/Log 365-388/DD1/7-18-69."
    - Unidentified Contents, 1 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3092)
  - Downtown -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 39.
    Police Drama
    - Downtown, 1986 May 7; open reel audio tape (Box 1035, Folder 13)
      On container, ""Downtown"/5-7-86/1k, 10k, 100Hz/Johnny Harris Music Corp."
  - The Equalizer -- Papers, Subseries 40.
    Plot: Robert McCall is "The Equalizer", a private detective with a lot of contacts who is available for hire if you have a problem that you don't know how to solve. His no-nonsense attitude, compassion, and experience with dealing with a wide variety of situations makes him a powerful and useful detective.
    - Press Information, 1986; 2 p. (Box 1859, Folder 16)
      Plot summaries for August 12 and August 19, 1986 episodes, as well as biographical information on star Edward Woodward.
    - Repeat Release Schedule no. 3, 1988 April 22; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 8)
      Includes air dates, original air dates, production numbers and episode titles.
  - Eve Arden Show -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 41.
    - Eve Arden Show, 1957 September 3; open reel audio tape (Box 1033, Folder 16)
      On container, "PB-1/CBS/Eve Arden/Good Takes Only/9-3-57."
  - Eyewitness to History -- Scores, Subseries 172.
    - Theme (Box 118)
  - Falcon Crest -- Papers, Subseries 42.
    - Press Information, 1986 September 18; 2 p. (Box 1859, Folder 17)
      Plot summaries and cast lists for two 1986 "Falcon Crest" episodes: October 10 and December 12.
  - Falcon Crest -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 43.
    - Dust to Dust., Cassette tape. (Box 1852)
      On container, " 'Six Selections from Dust to Dust' (Falcon Crest Episode)."
  - Fame -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 44.
    - Fame., Cassette tape. (Box 1852)
  - Flying High -- Papers, Subseries 45.
    - Beautiful People (episode title), 1978 October 5; 19 pages (Box 1844)
      Includes payroll lists and equipment receipts.
    - Bride & Groom (episode title), 1978 December 7; 14 pages (Box 1844)
      Includes: payroll lists; music recording schedule; handwritten note on musicians, and original CBS inter-office envelope.
    - Challenges (episode title), 1979 February 22; 18 pages (Box 1844)
      Includes payroll lists, equipment receipts, music recording schedule, freelance musician's payroll list, and the scoring session report.
    - Eye Openers (episode title), 1979 January 29-30; 15 pages (Box 1844)
      Includes: payroll lists; equipment receipts; musician's contracts (including contract for Arthur Ribinstein).
    - Great Expectations (episode title), 1975 November-1978 December; 23 pages (Box 1844)
      Materials related to the re-recording of two selections ("Old Greyhound" and "Evangelina") from the Flying High episode, "Great Expectations" for use on an A & M recording. Includes musicians' payroll lists as well as copies of A & M contracts with individual musicians.
    - Hairy Yak Plays (episode title), 1979 January 29; 13 pages (Box 1844)
      Includes payroll lists, musicians's contracts, and freelance musicians' payroll lists.
    - Just One of Those Days (episode title), 1978 September 25; 24 pages (Box 1844)
      Includes payroll lists and handwritten list of musicians.
    - The Great Escape (episode title), 1978 September 7; 17 pages (Box 1844)
    - [Assorted Papers] (Box 1861)
      Includes: freelance musician's payroll lists; service receipts; rental contracts; copyist, librarians and proofreaders contracts; orchestrators and arrangers contracts; handwritten notes, and orchestra manager's television film reports.
    - [Assorted Papers], 1979 January 11-November 30 (Box 1871)
      Includes: scoring session reports; orchestra manager's television film reports, and freelance musician's payroll lists.
    - Footage Cues, 1979 January 2; 13 pages (Box 1871)
  - Flying High -- Recording Logs, Subseries 46.
    - Brides and Grooms (episode title), 1978 December 2-3; 36 pages (Box 1758)
      Lists cues, timings, reel contents, and notes to the composer.
    - Challenges (episode title), 1979 February (Box 1758)
      Lists musicians, pay rates, studio, producing company, cues, recording session dates and times, etc.
    - Hairy Yak Plays (episode title), 1979 January (Box 1758)
      Eddie Robertson, orchestra manager.
    - Swan Song for an Ugly Duckling (episode title), 1978 November (Box 1758)
    - The Beautiful People (episode title), 1978 October 5; 3 pages (Box 1758)
      Lists cues, timings, recording location and time, and orchestration.
    - The Great Escape (episode title), 1978 September 7; 4 pages (Box 1758)
      Includes cues, names of musicians, notes on orchestration, and recording location and time.
    - Challenges (episode title), 1979 February 22; 1 p. (Box 1844)
    - Eye Openers (episode title), 1979 January 30; 1 pages (Box 1844)
    - Just One of Those Days (episode title), 1978 August 25; 3 pages (Box 1844)
    - [Episode Title Unknown], 1978 December 21; 1 pages (Box 1861)
      Production no. 0311-1555-0115.
    - [Episode Title Unknown], 1979 January 11; 1 pages (Box 1871)
      Production no. 0311-1555-0116.
    - Swan Song for an Ugly Duckling (Episode Title), 1978 November 30; 1 pages (Box 1871)
      Production no. 0113.
  - Flying High -- Scores, Subseries 47.
    - [Title Unidentified], 1 pages (Box 1844)
      Sketch for selection used in the Flying High episode, "The Great Escape."
  - Foley Square -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 48.
    - Unidentified, January 23, 1986; 2 in. tape (Box 1020, Folder 4)
      On container, "272/Foley Square/1-23-86/R3."
    - Unidentified, August 9, 1985; 2 in. tape (Box 1024, Folder 3)
      On container, "992/Foley Square/R-1/8-9-85."
    - Unidentified, August 9, 1985; 2 in. tape (Box 1024, Folder 4)
      On container, "Foley Sqare/R-2/8-9-85."
    - Unidentified, January 23, 1986; 2 in. tape (Box 1024, Folder 5)
      On container, "270/Foley Square/1-23-86/R2."
    - Logs 143-169, February 23, 1986; 1/2 in. tape (Box 1072, Folder 1)
      On container, "CED/2-23-86/R3/Logs 143-169/"Foley Square"."
    - Logs 84-142, February 23, 1986; open reel audio tape (Box 1072, Folder 14)
      On container, "CED/2-23-86/R2/Logs 84-142/"Foley Square"."
    - Logs 1-83, February 23, 1986; 1/2" tape (Box 1083, Folder 8)
      On container, "CED/2-23-86/R1/logs 1-83/"Foley Square"."
    - Logs 84-142, February 23, 1986; 1/2" tape (Box 1083, Folder 9)
      On container, "CED/2-23-86/R2/logs 84-142/"Foley Square"."
    - Logs 143-169, February 23, 1986; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1137, Folder 5)
      On container, "CED/2-23-86/R3/LOGS 143-169/"Foley Square"."
    - Foley Square., 1985 August 9; Cassette tape. (Box 1852)
      2 copies. On container, "All master takes."
    - Foley Square., Cassette tape. (Box 1852)
      On cassette, "'Foley Square' Music CBS Copyright 1985."
  - Freshman Year -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 49.
    - Unidentified, August 23, 1983; 2 in. tape (Box 968, Folder 5)
      On container, "R-3/Freshman Year/16 TRK/15 IRS/Non-Dolby/8-23-83/Prod# 0310-3211-0955."
    - Logs 3821-3839, August 23, 1983; 1/2" tape (Box 1058, Folder 13)
      On container, "CED/8-23-1983/R 128/logs 3821-3839/"first affair"."
    - Logs 3821-3839, August 23, 1983; open reel audio tape (Box 1058, Folder 16)
      On container, "CED/08-23-83/R173/logs 3821-3839/"first affair"."
    - Logs 3840-3870, August 23, 1983; 1/2" tape (Box 1058, Folder 14)
      On container, "CED/8-23-83/R129/logs 3840-3870/"first affair"."
    - Logs 3871-3893, August 23, 1983; 1/2" tape (Box 1058, Folder 15)
      On container, "CED/8-23-83/R130/logs 3871-3893/"First affair"."
    - Logs 4659-4677, September 5, 1984; open reel audio tape (Box 1058, Folder 17)
      On container, "CED/9-5-84/R210/logs 4659-4677/"paper castles"."
  - Funny Face--Sound Recordings, Subseries 146.
    - Unidentified Contents, 1 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3092)
  - General Electric Theater -- Recording Logs, Subseries 50.
    Also known as, "G.E. Theatre", and "G.E. Theater."
    - Season 8, Episode 18: Lear vs. the Committeeman, 1959 November 18 (Box 1166, Folder 10)
      On item, "The Commetteeman / Prod. #VT-104 / Music Log sent: 18 Nov. '59."